[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":164669,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":727228,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6 </sub>,  you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":26192,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":753430,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2367,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":755797,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":[" 5"],"rt":5679,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":761476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1674,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":763160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":10870,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":774030,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1793,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":775823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7512,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":783345,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1364,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":784710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the su m is 6 o r bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4150,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":788860,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1061,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":789921,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5932,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":795853,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2- 0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1206,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":797059,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3880,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":800939,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1093,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":802032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remembe r, to pe rform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":7660,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":809692,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1011,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":810703,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":8909,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":819612,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":930,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":820542,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3073,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":823615,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1106,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":824721,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":49029,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":873750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>).  Similarl y, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":72042,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":945792,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":21670,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":967462,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2074,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":969536,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse  of an e lement is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":8250,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":977786,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1530,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":979316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3391,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":982708,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":" Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1537,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":984245,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":5913,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":990168,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1273,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":991441,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? < br /><br  /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":8858,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":1000309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":15251,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":1015560,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":22492,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":1038052,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":54152,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":1092204,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element  which c an make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1097771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":3593,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1101374,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3572,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1104947,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's inco rrect. 5  is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":8833,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1113780,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":12003,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1125783,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</ sub>, be cause 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":13577,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1139360,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5644,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1145005,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":2819,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1147824,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new  operati on, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":13446,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1161270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3724,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1164994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1583,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1166577,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11- 0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":6330,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1172917,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3427,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1176354,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4964,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1181319,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6265,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1187585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":7408,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1194993,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The answer is 5 because 4 plus 1 equals 5, and 5 is less than 9.","response_history":["5","The ansd","The answer is 5 because four","The answer is 5 because fou","The answer is 5 because fo","The answer is 5 because f","The answer is 5 because 4 plus 1 equals 5, and 5 is less ta","The answer is 5 because 4 plus 1 equals 5, and 5 is less than 9."],"rt":46938,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1241931,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 because 8 plus 4 equals 12 and 12 minus 9 equals 3.","response_history":["3 because 8 plus 4 equals 12 and 12 mis","3 because 8 plus 4 equals 12 and 12 minus 9 equals 3."],"rt":37424,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1279355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 because if you add anything to it it returns the same number.","response_history":["0.","0 because 0 plus 0=9","0 because 0 plus 0=","0 because 0 plus 0+9","0 because 0 plus 0+","0 because 0 plus 0","0 because 0 plus ","0 because 0 plus","0 because 0 plu","0 because 0 pl","0 becau se 0 p","0 because 0 ","0 because 0","0 because ","0 because if you add anything to it it returns the same number."],"rt":157648,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1437004,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":29658,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1466662,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":3718,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1470380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 because 3 plus 6 equals 9","response_history":["6 because 3 plus 6 equals 9"],"rt":20000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1490380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because you cannot (get values??) for 1,3 and 5.","response_history":["No, because you cannot (get values??) for 1,3 and 5."],"rt":27974,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1518354,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No because you cannot return the numbers for 2 and 4.","response_history":["No because i","No because you cannot return the numbers f or 2 and  4."],"rt":21770,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1540125,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, because 5 can be multiplied (if this was in a class I would have to ask a question about how 1,2,3, and 4 were explained)","response_history":["Yes, because 5 can be multiplied (if this was in a class I wouldd","Yes, because 5 can be multiplied (if this was in a class I would have to ask a question about how 1234","Yes, because 5 can be multiplied (if this was in a class I would have to ask a question about how 1,234","Yes, because 5 can be multiplied (if this was in a class I would have to ask a question about how 1,2.34","Yes, because 5 can be multiplied (if this was in a class I would have to ask a question about how 1,2,.34","Yes, because 5 can be multipli ed (if t his was in a class I would have to ask a question about how 1,2,34","Yes, because 5 can be multiplied (if this was in a class I would have to ask a question about how 1,2,3,4","Yes, because 5 can be multiplied (if this was in a class I would have to ask a question about how 1,2,3, 4","Yes, because 5 can be multiplied (if this was in a class I would have to ask a question about how 1,2,3, a4","Yes, because 5 can be multiplied (if this was in a class I would have to ask a question about how 1,2,3, an4","Yes, because 5 can be multiplied (if this was in a class I would have to ask a question about how 1,2,3, and4","Yes, because 5 can be multiplied (if this was in a class I would have to ask a question about how 1,2,3, and 4 were explained)"],"rt":76650,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1616775,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"f ree","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that here. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator because of the number 7, I think? 6 would not be a generator under that conclusion as well, but again if I was in a class, I would need this explained again.","response_history":["No, and I sumbit","No, and I sumbi","No, and I sumb","No, and I sum","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong,. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, . Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, s. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my l ast answ er right when I realized I was wrong, so . Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd . Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd l. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd li. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd lik. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my  last an swer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like . Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like t. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to . Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to c. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to co. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to cor. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to corr. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was  wrong, s o I'd like to corre. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correc. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct . Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct t. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct th. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct tha. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right  when I  realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that . Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that h. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that he. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that her. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that here. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator becua","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that here. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator becu","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that here. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator because of the number 7, I think? I","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I  realized  I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that here. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator because of the number 7, I think? 6 would also","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that here. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator because of the number 7, I think? 6 would als","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that here. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator because of the number 7, I think? 6 would al","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that here. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator because of the number 7, I think? 6 would a","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that here. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator because of the number 7, I think? 6 would ","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that here. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator becaus e of the  number 7, I think? 6 would","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that here. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator because of the number 7, I think? 6 would not be a generator under that conclusion as well, but again if I was in a class, I would need this explained again/","No, and I submitted my last answer right when I realized I was wrong, so I'd like to correct that here. Under +9 5 is NOT a generator because of the number 7, I think? 6 would not be a generator under that conclusion as well, but again if I was in a class, I would need this explained again."],"rt":134953,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1751728,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operat ion, you  can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":30180,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1781908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+1n=0","response_history":["1+1n=0"],"rt":38820,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1820728,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"-X+Xn=0 This is all I can come up with, and I have written it out, but I can't explain the procedure.","response_history":["x+","x=+m","x=+n ","x=+n-+n B","x=+n-+n X is going to return z","x=+n-+n X is going to ret urn )"," x=+n-+n X is going to return 0 so ","x X is going to return 0 so "," X is going to return 0 so ","X X is going to return 0 so ","X= X is going to return 0 so ","X X is going to return 0 so ","X+ X is going to return 0 so ","X+n X is going to return 0 so ","X+n+ X is going to return 0 so ","X+Xn+ X is going to return 0 so ","X+Xn X is going to return 0 so ","X+Xn= X is going to return 0 so ","X+Xn=X is going to return 0 so ","X+Xn= is going to return 0 so ","X+Xn=0 is going to return 0 so ","X+Xn=0 \\","X+Xn=0 X","X+0Xn=0 X","X+0n=0 X","X+0n=-0 X","X+0n=-X0 X","X+0n=-X X","X+0n=-XX","X+0n=-X","-X+Xn=0 This is all I can come up with, and I have written it out, but I can't explain the proceud","-X+Xn=0 This is all I can come up with, and I have written it out, but I can't explain the proceu","-X+Xn=0 This is all I can come up with, and I have written it out, but I can't explain the procedure."],"rt":617876,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2438604,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any number lower than itself. It needs to be a multiple that creates a number higher than it is. So when it said 5 WAS a generator, it was because 5 would bring it over the threshold of 9.","response_history":["It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any number under","It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any ","It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any","It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any number lower than itsle","It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any number lower than itsl","It appears that it needs to be a number than  can cre ate any number lower than itself. So the example ","It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any number lower than itself. So the example","It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any number lower than itself. So ","It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any number lower than itself. So","It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any number lower than itself. S","It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any number lower than itself. ","It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any number lower than itself. It needs to be a multiple that creates a number high ","It appears that it needs to be a number than can create any number lower than itself. It needs to be a multiple that creates a number higher than it is. So when it said 5 WAS a generator, it was because 5 would bring it over the threshold of 9."],"rt":113104,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2551708,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":8356,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2560064,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":16757,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2576821,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":8933,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2585754,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"If x is not higher than the generator it is a multiple","response_history":["I","If x is not higher than the generator","If x is not higher than the generato","If x is not higher than the generator it is a multiple"],"rt":55854,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2641608,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":7669,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2649277,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I can't. I don't understand this far along since I would have had questions, and I don't understand the divisor portion.","response_history":["I can't. I don't understand this far along since I would have had questions, and I don't understand the divisor portion."],"rt":36103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2685380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":2429,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2687809,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1509,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2689319,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"41","response_history":["41"],"rt":3052,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2692372,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors  Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":3042,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2695414,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"AlgebraII","response_history":["Ale","Algebra!!","Algebra!1","Algebra!","AlgebraII"],"rt":16141,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2711555,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - us ed it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3393,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2714958,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2720525,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 -  definit ely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4934,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2725459,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":3972,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2729431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2727,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2732168,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":" multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2363,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2734531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4266,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2738797,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":7998,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2746795,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I would have like to have felt like I was successful, but I did feel like it skipped far ahead once it was to the multiple/divisor section.","response_history":["I would have like to have felt like I was successful, but I did feel like it skipped far ahead once it was to the multiple/divisor section."],"rt":42658,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2789453,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]